♪ Theme music playing  ♪
♪ Game of Thrones 4x07 ♪
Mockingbird
Original Air Date on May 18. 2014
== sync. corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
♪ Theme music ends  ♪
I made a deal for you
to keep your ungrateful head
on your ungrateful neck
a little while longer.
I'm sorry.
what am I grateful for?
The opportunity to live
and die at the Wall
as punishment for a crime
I did not commit?
You threw your life away.
You threw it away.
It's not a joke.
You understand that. don't you?
Of course it's a joke.
just not a very funny one.
I couldn't--
I couldn't listen to her
standing there
telling her lies.
I couldn't do it.
You fell in love
with a whore.
Yes. I fell in love
And I was stupid enough to think
that she had fallen in love with me.
That deal you made.
it was everything
Father wanted.
You do see that?
He gets you back
as his heir.
The future
Lord of the Rock.
And he ships me off
to Castle Black.
out of sight at last.
All so perfect.
It felt good
to take that from him.
He knows I'm innocent and he's
willing to sacrifice me anyway.
He's willing
to sacrifice any of us.
Not you.
You're the golden son.
You could kill a king.
lose a hand.
fuck your own sister.
you'll always be the golden son.
Careful.
I'm the last friend
you've got.
At least I got to tell
them what they really are.
Yes. brilliant speech.
They'll be talking
about it for days to come.
I thought you were
a realist.
Didn't realize
you'd die for pride.
Don't give up on me
just yet.
I survived one
trial by combat.
even though you weren't
there to save me.
I can't save you
this time either.
My training has proved
that I can't beat
a stable boy with my left hand.
Where's your sense
of adventure?
Even if you lose.
imagine the look
on Father's face
when you fall.
Our family name snuffed out
with a single swing
of the sword.
It is tempting.
Well...
Bronn fought for me once.
he'll do it again.
If he wins.
I expect I'll be
in his debt
for the rest
of my life.
If he wins.
Will you find him for me?
Who does Cersei plan
on naming as a champion?
I hope it's Ser Meryn Trant.
I'd enjoy watching Bronn
disembowel that pompous child beater.
No.
Not Ser Meryn.
Go on. move it.
And you.
Come on.
Mercy.
Please.
Please. mercy.
Ser Gregor.
Welcome to the capital.
Thank you for riding
here so quickly.
You seem to be
in good form.
Who am I fighting?
Does it matter?
Could be food.
Could be soldiers.
You shouldn't be sitting
out here like this.
Where else to sit?
Tried to walk back
to my hut.
hurt too much.
Then I remembered
they burned my hut down.
Who were "they"?
I stopped asking
a while ago.
That's not gonna
get better.
Doesn't seem so.
A bad way to go.
Haven't you had enough?
Of what?
I know.
Time to go.
Take matters into
my own hands.
The thought
has occurred to me.
So why go on?
Habit.
Nothing could
be worse than this.
Maybe nothing is
worse than this.
Nothing isn't better
or worse than anything.
Nothing is just nothing.
Who are you?
My name is Arya.
Arya Stark.
You her father?
Her captor.
Bringing her to her aunt
for ransom.
A fair exchange.
that is.
Always held to the notion
of fair exchange
in all my dealings.
You give me.
I give you.
Fair.
A balance.
No balance anymore.
Could I have
a drink?
Dying is thirsty work.
Wish it were wine.
So do I.
That's where the heart is.
That's how you kill a man.
The fuck you doing?
There's a price
on your head.
Guess that's what the king does
when you tell him to fuck off.
The king's dead.
He drank poisoned wine
at his own wedding.
The bounty on you is for
killing Lannister soldiers.
100 silver stags.
And you thought you
were going to collect it?
Didn't think very hard.
did you?
You were Yoren's prisoners when
he was taking me to the Wall.
He told me he'd fuck
me bloody with a stick.
This day's really not working out
the way you planned.
He on your little list?
He can't be.
I don't know his name.
What's your name?
- Rorge.
- Thank you.
You're learning.
Rangers returning!
They return!
- Rangers returning!
- Greetings.
Didn't think I'd see
you again.
All right. Jon?
Welcome back. brother.
Lord Snow.
This is no place
for wild beasts.
Lock him away
or I'll let Hobb throw him
in tonight's stew.
Come on. Ghost.
Mance's army was closing in
on Craster's Keep when we left.
We saw their campfires
from Osric's Hill.
They'll reach the Wall
before the next full moon.
I'm surprised you didn't
ride over and say hello.
The King-beyond-the-Wall
is your old friend. isn't he?
We need to prepare.
We've been preparing.
We should seal the tunnel.
Plug it with rocks
and ice.
Flood it
and let it freeze.
And how would we
range north?
- We wouldn't.
- Coward.
You would cut off
our legs.
pluck out our eyes.
leave us cowering
behind the Wall
hoping for the storm
to pass?
We can't defend the gate
against 100.000 men.
This castle has stood
for thousands of years.
The Night's Watch has defended
her for thousands of years.
And in all those centuries. we have
never sealed the tunnel.
Have you ever seen
a giant. Ser Alliser?
I have.
The tunnel's gate
won't stop them.
The bars on those gates
are four inches thick.
Cold-rolled steel.
They won't stop them.
Remind me which order
you belong to. Lord Snow.
The stewards.
Are the stewards responsible
for maintaining the tunnel?
No.
Who would that be?
- The builders.
- Ah. the builders.
First Builder Yarwyck.
Lord Snow here recommends
sealing the tunnel.
leaving us unable
to carry out our duties
as sworn brothers
of the Night's Watch.
Do you agree with him?
No.
Given your deep knowledge of
the wildling army. Lord Snow.
you and Tarly will take
night duties atop the Wall
until the full moon.
Moving on.
First Builder. we'll need 100 barrels
of pitch brought atop the wall.
Aye.
My lord.
You have new clothes.
Do you like 'em?
Eh?
Gloves are doeskin.
Softer than
a virgin's thighs.
I sent for you
days ago.
- I've been a bit busy.
- Doing what?
My lonesome
bachelor days are over.
I'm to wed
Lollys Stokeworth.
Lollys Stokeworth?
She doesn't strike me
as your sort of girl.
I wouldn't say I had
a single sort of girl.
She's dim-witted.
If I wanted wits.
I'd marry you.
When my sister arranged
this love match.
did she mention that Lollys
has an older sister?
Falyse.
Aye. I did know
about the older sister.
And you understand
the rules of inheritance?
Falyse is 40
and barren.
She still gets Castle Stokeworth
when her father dies.
She does.
Unless she happens
to perish before her father.
Then Lollys gets the castle.
What? Ladies fall
from their horses
and snap their pretty
necks all the time.
You and my sister
deserve each other.
Why did you bother
to come here?
You once said if anyone ever asked
me to sell you out.
you'd double their price.
Is it two wives you want
or two castles?
One of each will do.
But if you want me
to kill the Mountain for you.
it'd better be
a damn big castle.
I'm bit short
on castles at the moment.
But I can offer you
gold and gratitude.
I have gold.
What can I buy
with gratitude?
You might be surprised.
A Lannister always
pays his debts.
Your sister's
a Lannister. too.
My wife is heir
to Winterfell.
If I emerge from this
with my head still on my shoulders.
I may one day rule
the North in her name.
I could carve you out
a big piece of it.
If and may and could.
It's bloody
cold up north.
Lollys is soft and warm.
And close.
If I gave you the choice
between fucking Lollys
and fighting the Mountain.
you'd have your britches down
and your cock out
before I could blink.
Does he frighten
you so much?
I'd be a bloody fool
if he didn't frighten me.
He's freakish big
and freakish strong.
And quicker than
you'd expect for a man of that size.
Maybe I could take him.
dance around
until he's so tired
of hacking at me.
he dropped his sword.
get him off
his feet somehow.
But one misstep...
...and I'm dead.
Why should I risk it?
Because you're my friend.
Aye. I'm your friend.
And when have you ever
risked your life for me?
I like you.
pampered little shit
that you are.
I just like myself more.
I understand.
I'm sorry it has
to be this way.
Why are you sorry?
Because you're
an evil bastard
with no conscience
and no heart?
That's what I liked about
you in the first place.
We had some
good days together.
Yes. we did.
What will you do?
I suppose I'll have to kill
the Mountain myself.
Won't that make
for a great song?
I hope to hear
them sing it one day.
How did you get in here?
Your door is well guarded.
but your window is not.
I swam to an island
a mile offshore for these.
Don't do that again.
Never met a woman who
didn't like wildflowers.
These are my
private quarters.
If I want you here.
I will summon you.
Forgive me. my queen.
I live to serve you.
Tell me why you're here.
I came to ask a favor.
I only have two talents
in this world--
war and women.
You are staying here
in Meereen to rule.
That is a wise decision.
I respect it.
But here in Meereen.
I cannot pursue my talents.
I've ordered the Second Sons
to patrol the streets
to stop
the revenge killing.
You've ordered us
to be night watchmen.
And as for women.
there are thousands
in Meereen you can pursue.
There is only one.
and she does not
want me.
You swore me your sword.
My sword is yours
till the day I die.
So if I command you
to stay in Meereen
and patrol the streets?
I'll stay in Meereen
and patrol the streets.
Send me to kill
your enemies.
Any enemy anywhere.
Let me do
what I do best.
Very well.
Do what you do best.
Take off your clothes.
Oh.
Come in. my queen.
Please.
I didn't mean
to disturb you. my lady.
You could never
disturb me.
I just wanted to speak
with you before we left.
Could you bring me
that vial over there?
The blue one.
No. no. no.
Not that one.
You don't even want
to touch that one.
Next to it.
That's the one.
When I looked into
the flames this morning.
the Lord spoke to me.
He said.
"Tonight. you will have your
last good bath in a long while.
Make it count."
A joke.
Not a very good one.
I'm afraid.
It was. I--
humor isn't my strength.
That's because
st jokes are lies
and you're devoted
to the truth.
If they're lies. my lady.
aren't they best avoided?
Not always.
Most of these powders
and potions
are lies.
Deceptions to make men
think they witnessed our Lord's power.
Once they step into his light.
they will see the lie for what it was--
a trick that led them
to the truth.
A pinch of this powder
in a bonfire
will send a flaming column
screaming towards the sky.
And this one creates
a black smoke
that will make the bravest
man piss himself with fear.
And a drop of this
in any man's wine
will drive him
wild with lust.
Did you use it
with Stannis?
No.
Don't be upset.
Men never crave
what they already have.
It's only flesh.
It needs
what it needs.
No act done in service
of the Lord
can ever be called a sin.
I thank God every day
for bringing you to us.
And Stannis to you.
He wants to bring
Shireen with us.
I think that would be
ill-advised.
My daughter has heretical tendencies.
as you're well aware.
I don't know if her doubt is real
or simply meant to spite me.
but whichever the case.
she should stay home.
I understand
how you feel.
Hmm.
But that
is impossible.
Why?
You don't need powders
and potions. my queen.
You don't need lies.
You are strong enough to look into
the Lord's light
and see his truth
for yourself.
However harsh it is.
However hard for us
to understand.
You don't need my help.
but I will need yours soon.
When we set sail.
your daughter must be with us.
The Lord needs her.
Jorah the Andal.
Are you here
to see our queen?
She's in a good mood.
Khaleesi.
- You're here early.
- Later than some.
You don't approve?
It's not a question of approval.
it's a question of trust.
You neither
approve nor trust.
Why would I?
The man's a sellsword.
Didn't you fight for
the Golden Company
before pledging
your sword to my brother?
I did.
I trust you.
Daario Naharis
killed his captains
and dumped their heads at your feet
when he grew tired of their commands.
How could you ever have
faith in a man like that?
I could never have faith
in a man like Daario.
That's why I've sent him and
the Second Sons to retake Yunkai.
- You have?
- I have.
Without you there
to rule. Khaleesi.
I fear the masters
will simply bide their time.
wait for the invaders
to leave and reassert control.
That is why I've ordered Daario
to execute every master in Yunkai.
The masters tear babies
from their mothers' arms.
They mutilate little boys
by the thousands.
They train little girls
in the art of pleasuring old men.
They treat men like beasts.
as you said yourself.
Herding the masters into pens
and slaughtering them by the thousands
is also treating men
like beasts.
The slaves you freed.
brutality is all
they've ever known.
If you want them to know
something else.
you'll have
to show it to them.
And repay the slavers
with what? Kindness?
A fine?
A stern warning?
It's tempting to see
your enemies as evil. all of them.
but there's good and evil
on both sides in every war ever fought.
Let the priests argue
over good and evil.
Slavery is real.
I can end it.
I will end it.
And I will end
those behind it.
I sold men
into slavery. Khaleesi.
And now you are helping me
show them to freedom.
I wouldn't be here to help you
if Ned Stark had done to me
what you want to do
to the masters of Yunkai.
The man who came to me
the other day about burying his father.
Hizdahr zo Loraq?
He will accompany
the Second Sons
and serve as my ambassador
to Yunkai.
He will tell the masters
what has happened in Meereen.
He will explain the choice
they have before them.
They can live
in my new world
or they can die
in their old one.
Well. go and catch Daario
before he leaves.
Tell him
I changed my mind.
Yes. Khaleesi.
No.
Tell him you
changed my mind.
Rat cunts.
Fucking whore.
You're doing it wrong.
You need to burn away
that horrible bit there.
Otherwise it's gonna
get infected and fester.
I know you don't like fire.
but if you don't do it right--
No fire.
It'll only take a second.
- It won't hurt that much.
- No fire!
Shut up about it.
Shut up about everything.
Thanks to you.
I'm a walking bag of silver
anywhere the Lannisters
hold sway.
Which is everywhere
between where we are now
and where we're going.
I'm as stupid as that hog
you stuck back in the village.
getting myself cut
and stabbed and bitten.
No reward is worth
this much trouble.
Wish I'd never
laid eyes on you.
You say your brother
gave you that sword.
My brother gave me this.
It was just like you said
a while back.
Pressed me to the fire
like I was a nice
juicy mutton chop.
Why?
Thought I stole
one of his toys.
I didn't steal it.
I was just playing with it.
The pain was bad.
The smell was worse.
But the worst thing
was that it was my brother who did it.
My father.
who protected him...
told everyone my bedding
caught fire.
You think
you're on your own?
Let me wash it out
and help you
sew it up at least.
Bit of comfort
never hurt anyone.
We've been sleeping in
ditches the last few weeks.
I think we can treat
ourselves to a featherbed for the night
and a hot meal
not cooked by you.
Couldn't agree
more. my lady.
Just don't start expecting
silk underclothes.
Not working for your
former lord any longer.
- Yes. my lady.
- Don't get drunk.
No. my lady.
Can I get you
anything else?
No. this will do
nicely. thank you.
Kidney pie is wonderful.
Thanks.
I do my best.
A good kidney pie is all
about the ingredients.
Flour. lard. water.
eggs. milk.
Easy enough.
But the meat.
peacetime or not. getting your hands on
a good bottom round steak
and calves' kidneys
is not easy.
I mean. some people settle
for plain old beef kidneys.
Got no right to cook
anything. them.
Oh. and the gravy.
Don't get me started
on the gravy.
Very difficult
to get right.
See. a lot of people
give up on the gravy.
You cannot give up
on the gravy.
No gravy. no pie.
Simple as that.
That's nice armor.
Are you a knight?
No.
Oh. it's just people with
armor are usually knights.
Generally speaking.
From King's Landing. though. aren't you?
From there myself originally.
Flea Bottom born and bred.
What brings you
to these parts?
We're looking
for someone.
Someone in particular?
Maybe they came in here.
A lot of people come in here.
Just the other day we had 17--
A girl. tall. red hair.
very pretty.
Her name is Sansa Stark.
but she may be using a different name.
Starks?
What. like them lot
from "Winterhell"?
No. ain't seen
anyone like that.
I heard they was
all traitors.
Don't need
no traitors in here.
I pledged my life to
their mother Catelyn Stark.
I swore to her I'd bring
her daughters home.
Sure I can't get you
a bit more kidney pie?
What?
It's nothing. my lady.
You wouldn't be screwing
your face up like that if it was nothing.
Don't want to offend. my lady.
Truly. I don't.
You're not interesting
enough to be offensive.
The Lannisters
want Lady Sansa.
have money.
People kill for money.
I don't think we should
be telling people
we're searching
for Lady Sansa.
My lady. My lord.
Could I have a word?
What about?
Not kidney pie.
You seem
like a proper lady.
Someone who could
be trusted.
I never met no Sansa Stark.
But I know her sister...
Arya.
No one's seen Arya Stark
since her father was beheaded.
She's presumed dead.
She weren't when I last
spoke to her.
When was that?
Heading up north with
the Night's Watch.
She was all dressed up
as a boy.
Like your ladyship.
only without the armor.
Going by the name Arry.
- So what happened to her?
- Well--
The quick version.
The Lannisters
took us prisoner.
We escaped.
The Brotherhood took
us prisoner.
They sold me
to the innkeep.
They were gonna sell Arya
to her mother at Riverrun
along with another prisoner.
Big ugly fellow.
Foul mouth
and a face like
a half-burnt ham.
- Not friendly.
- The Hound.
That's the one.
If you find her.
could you give her this?
She liked the last one
I gave her.
but. well. this one
turned out better.
Um. you were saying?
Her mother's dead.
grandfather's dead.
Walder Frey is
the new lord of Riverrun.
The Brotherhood
isn't going to Riverrun.
They'll take her
to the Eyrie. my lady.
Why the Eyrie?
Her aunt. Lysa Arryn.
Catelyn Stark's sister.
She's Arya's last living
relative with money.
She hates the Lannisters.
Lord Tyrion
made sure I knew
which house married which
and who hated who.
Sansa could
be there. too.
Aye. my lady.
Could be.
You sure about this?
No.
I imagined you'd be back
at the brothel at this hour.
I did spend some time
with an absolutely stunning
blonde the other day.
Mm. do tell.
I've got every kind
of filth down here
except the kind I like.
Your sister.
Oh.
Cersei approached me.
We spoke a great deal
about her daughter.
How worried your sister
is about her.
She was trying
very hard to pretend
she had not come
to sway me against you.
I think she may have even
believed it herself.
Making honest feelings
do dishonest work
is one of her many gifts.
It was difficult for her
to hide her true intentions.
It is rare
to meet a Lannister
who shares my enthusiasm
for dead Lannisters.
She desperately wants
to see you killed.
She didn't need
to bother you.
It looks as though
I've taken care of that myself.
The joy she will feel
when my head
leaves my neck.
She's wanted this
for a long time.
Yes. I know.
We met. you and I.
Many years ago.
I think I would
have remembered that.
Unlikely.
You had just been born.
Our father brought me
and my sister Elia with him
on a visit
to Casterly Rock.
My first time
away from Dorne.
I didn't like anything
about the Rock.
Not the food.
not the weather.
not your accents.
Nothing.
But the biggest
disappointment...
you.
You and my family have more
in common than you might admit.
The whole way from Dorne
all anyone talked about
was the monster
that had been born
to Tywin Lannister.
A head twice
the size of his body.
a tail between his legs.
claws. one red eye.
the privates of both
a girl and a boy.
That would have made
things so much easier.
When we met your sister. she promised
she would show you to us.
Every day we would ask.
Every day she would
say. "Soon."
Then she and your brother
took us
to your nursery and...
she unveiled the freak.
Your head
was a bit large.
Your arms and legs
were a bit small.
but no claw.
No red eye.
No tail between your legs.
Just a tiny pink cock.
We didn't try to hide
our disappointment.
"That's not a monster."
I told Cersei.
"That's just a baby."
And she said.
"He killed my mother."
And she pinched
your little cock so hard.
I thought she might
pull it off.
Until your brother
made her stop.
"It doesn't matter."
she told us.
"Everyone says
he will die soon.
I hope they are right.
He should not
have lived this long."
Well...
sooner or later. Cersei always gets
what she wants.
And what about
what I want?
Justice
for my sister
and her children.
If you want justice.
you've come
to the wrong place.
I disagree.
I've come to
the perfect place.
I want to bring those
who have wronged me to justice.
And all those who have
wronged me are right here.
I will begin with
Ser Gregor Clegane.
who killed
my sister's children
and then raped her
with their blood still on his hands
before killing her. too.
I will be your champion.
Hello. Robin.
What are you doing?
I'm building my home.
Winterfell.
At least I think I am.
I haven't been back there
in a very long time.
Why did you leave?
It's a long story.
I stay here in the Eyrie.
Mother says it's dangerous on the roads
and I have to keep myself safe
because I'm the Lord
of the Vale
and the Lord of the Vale
is a very important person.
Yes. you certainly are.
When will you go back?
Probably never.
My family doesn't
live there anymore
and someone
burned it down.
Oh.
Does Winterfell
have a Moon Door?
No. I'm afraid not.
It's not high up in the mountains.
It's down on the ground.
That sounds dangerous.
- How do you make people fly?
- We don't.
What do you do with
all the bad people
and the scary people
and the people you don't like?
I never did anything
with them at all.
Girls didn't take part
in that where I came from.
Well. I'm Lord
of the Vale.
When I grow up. I'll be able to fly
anybody who bothers me.
Or you.
When we get married.
you can tell me
if you don't like somebody
and then we can bring them
back here and. whoosh!
Right through
the Moon Door.
I like the sound of that.
Let's put a Moon Door
in your Winterfell.
All right.
It can go in here
in this big tower.
Careful.
You've ruined it.
Now I'm going to have
to rebuild the whole thing.
- I didn't ruin it.
- You did.
It was already ruined
because it didn't have a Moon Door.
I was fixing it.
Knocking things down
isn't fixing them.
- It's ruining them.
- I didn't ruin it!
- You're being stupid.
Robin. I'm sorry. I--
Children.
- I hit him.
- Yes. I saw.
I shouldn't have done that.
No. his mother
should have
a long time ago.
Consider it a step
in the right direction.
If he tells Aunt Lysa...
Let me worry about
Aunt Lysa.
I was trying to remember
what everything looked like.
I'll never see it again.
A lot can happen
between now and never.
If you want to build
a better home.
first you must
demolish the old one.
Why did you really
kill Joffrey?
Tell me why.
I loved your mother more
than you could ever know.
Given the opportunity.
what do we do to those
who've hurt
the ones we love?
In a better world.
one where love
could overcome
strength and duty.
you might have been
my child.
But we don't live
in that world.
You're more beautiful
than she ever was.
Lord Baelish...
Call me Petyr.
You wanted
to see me. Aunt Lysa?
Come here. Sansa.
Do you know how far
the fall is?
No.
Neither do I. precisely.
Hundreds of feet.
It's fascinating
what happens to bodies when they
hit the rocks from such a height.
The impact breaks them
right apart.
Like eggs dropped
on the floor.
Sometimes pieces
remain intact.
You'll find the head
sitting on its own.
Every hair in place.
Blue eyes staring
at nothing.
I know what you did.
I'm so sorry. Aunt Lysa.
I never should have hit Robin.
I know it. I promise it won't happen--
Don't be coy with me.
you little whore.
You kissed him.
You kissed Petyr.
- I didn't. You don't understand.
- I saw you.
You can't lie to me because
I saw it with my own eyes.
- He kissed me. I pulled away.
- Liar!
Whore! He is mine!
My father. my husband.
my sister.
they all stood between us
and now they're all dead.
That's what happens to people
who stand between Petyr and me.
Look down!
Look down! Look down!
Lysa!
Let her go.
You want her?
This empty-headed child?
Let her go.
She's just like her mother.
She'll never love you.
I lied for you.
I killed for you.
Why did you bring
her here? Why?
I'll send her away.
I swear on my life.
I swear to all the gods.
Let her go. Lysa.
Oh. my sweet wife.
My sweet. silly wife.
I have only loved
one woman...
only one.
my entire life.
Your sister.
== sync. corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ Music playing  ♪
♪ Music ends  ♪
Press play. Subtitles appear.
200+ languages. One app:  tryray.app